<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Cybermen Factions+</name>
  <author>Crazya</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>

  <packageId>Crazya.Cybermen.Factions</packageId>
  <description>
    This mods adds the ablitiy to play the popular race from the british show, Doctor who, the Cybermen.
    You are able to play Cybermen as well as have a faction on the map to fight against.
    This mod requires a new save or a faction mod that lets you load factions into your current game.
    
    This mod also lets you create an upgrade kit to convert your pawns into Cybermen. Please note, this function is a work in progress and can change. Currently it adds only psychopath to the traits. 

    Credits:
    MVP: Ogliss- He has been there every step of the way and taught me everything I know, super grateful for the time he spares to assit me! He also created the function of converting your inferior humans into Cybermen!
    Art: All textures are created by Odz!
    Sound: Sound has been taken from SWDTeam (minecraft doctor who mod)


     Know issues:
     A couple of errors can sometimes be thrown during the converstion operation, these can be ignored! (They are harmless). 

    In progress plans:
    Dalek Faction and playable race is in progress. (hoping to include a Human Dalek form!- maybe on its own)
    Doctor who based Weapon mod pack. (cybermen and Dalek)

    Future plans:
    Maybe more Doctor who races.
    Maybe some doctors?

    This is my first mod, so please know this is still a work in progress.
    
    License:
    Feel free to edit or update this mod in the event I vanish. all I ask is give the correct credits!
  </description>

  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/RimWorld-CCL-Reborn/AlienRaces</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadBefore>

  </loadBefore>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>